if the only copies you have for your
如果你只有一份复印件
logo are rasterized formats like PNG and
徽标是光栅化格式，如PNG和
jpg then you won't be able to reap the
Jpg，那么你就不能收获
benefits of having a vector SVG file
拥有矢量SVG文件的好处
like infinite scaling and being able to
就像无限的扩展和能够
edit your logo in the future in that
在该中编辑您将来的徽标
case you'll need to generate a vector
如果您需要生成一个向量
copy of your logo using vector design
使用矢量设计复制您的徽标
software and that's what I'll be
软件，这就是我要做的
demonstrating in this video this is Nick
在这段视频中演示这位是尼克
with logos by Nick comm and in this
尼克·科姆的徽标和这个
tutorial I'll be demonstrating two
教程，我将演示两个
different ways in which you can take a
你可以用不同的方式
logo in PNG format and trace a vector
PNG格式的徽标和跟踪矢量
SVG copy of it but before we get started
SVG副本，但在我们开始之前
if you'd like to learn more about how
如果您想了解更多有关如何
Inkscape works be sure to check out my
Inkscape作品一定要查看我的
Inkscape masterclass it's a collection
Inkscape大师类它是一个集合
of over 60 videos where I go over every
有60多个视频，我每看一遍
tool and feature in Inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what it is and demonstrate how
解释它是什么，并演示它如何
it works I'll have a link in the
它起作用了，我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out so getting started as you
请查看这一点，以便像您一样开始
can see I have Inkscape opened up here
可以看到我在这里打开了Inkscape
on my screen and the first thing I want
在我的屏幕上，我想要的第一件事
to do is just set up the documents that
要做的就是设置文档，
we are all working with a similar layout
我们都在使用类似的布局
I want to come up here to where it says
我想上到上面写着的地方
enable snapping and turn that off and
启用捕捉并将其关闭，然后
then I want to come up here to where it
然后我想来这里，在那里
says view make sure we have custom
说VIEW确保我们有客户
selected and then come over here to
选中，然后到这里来
where it says view go to zoom view zoom
上面写着查看转到缩放视图缩放
and zoom in at 1 to 1 so what I'm going
以1比1的比例放大，所以我要做的是
to do now is I'm going to import my PNG
现在要做的是我要导入我的PNG
logo into Inkscape and the way that I'm
Inkscape的徽标和我的方式
going to do that is by opening the
要做到这一点，请打开
folder where it's located and in
它所在的文件夹和
clicking and dragging the file onto the
单击该文件并将其拖到
canvas now you won't be able to see me
画布现在你看不到我了
doing this because I have the folder
这样做是因为我有文件夹
opened up on my other monitor but I am
在我的另一台显示器上打开，但我
clicking and dragging the file onto the
单击该文件并将其拖到
canvas they are in Inkscape now we're
画布他们在Inkscape中，现在我们
gonna hit this little menu that pops up
我要点击弹出的这个小菜单
I'm going to choose embed I'm going to
我要选择Embedd，我要
choose default import resolution and
选择默认导入分辨率并
then I'm going to choose none I'll click
然后，我将选择None，然后单击
OK and there you can see that is the
好的，你可以看到这是
Inkscape logo that I will be using for
我将使用的Inkscape徽标
this demonstration now let me just zoom
这个演示现在让我只需放大
in on this just to show you that this is
参与进来只是为了向你展示这是
indeed a raster format this is not a
这确实是一种栅格格式，而不是
vector design so let me zoom back out
矢量设计，让我把它放大
here what I want to do now is I want to
我现在想做的是，我想
change the size of my page border so
更改页面边框的大小，以便
that it fits the size of the logo here
它与这里的徽标大小相符
so to do that I'm going to select the
要做到这一点，我将选择
logo as you can see here and go to file
您可以在此处看到徽标并转到文件
properties and I want to expand this
属性，我想扩展这一点
menu that says resize page to content
显示调整页面大小以适应内容的菜单
and then down here where it says resize
然后在这里，上面写着调整大小
page to drawing or selection go ahead
前进到绘图或选择的页面
and click that and it's going to change
然后点击它，它就会改变
the page boundaries to where the logo is
徽标所在位置的页面边界
so let me go ahead and close out of that
所以让我继续下去，结束这个话题
so like I said at the beginning of the
所以就像我在开始的时候说的
video there's two different ways where
视频有两种不同的方式
we can go about tracing a vector copy of
我们可以开始追踪一份
this design one is an easier way where
这种设计是一种更简单的方式，
it's kind of like an auto trace function
它有点像一个自动跟踪功能
using the trace bitmap feature and if
使用跟踪位图功能，如果
your design is so complicated that that
你们的设计如此复杂，以至于
won't work you'll have to manually trace
不会起作用的，你必须手动追踪
it so I'm gonna show you both on you
所以我要给你们两个看看
show you the auto trace feature first I
首先向您展示自动跟踪功能
want to select the logo just make sure
想要选择徽标，只需确保
you have the logo selected here you'll
您在此处选择了徽标，您将
notice you have it selected when you see
请注意，当您看到以下内容时，您已将其选中
these arrows enabled and I want to come
这些箭头启用了，我想来
up here to where it says path and I want
在这上面写着路径和我想要的
to go to trace bitmap and under this
转到跟踪位图并在此下方
menu we have these two different options
菜单我们有这两个不同的选项
single scan and multiple scans for this
对此进行单次扫描和多次扫描
design it's just black and white so I'm
设计它是黑白的，所以我
going to leave it as single scan if your
如果您的数据显示为单次扫描，
design has colors you might want to
设计中有你可能想要的颜色
click on multiple scans and then you can
单击多个扫描，然后您可以
choose the number of colors in the scan
选择扫描中的颜色数量
right there but this design is just
就在那里，但这个设计只是
black and white so I'm gonna leave it a
黑白的，所以我要把它留下来
single scan I'm going to leave these
单次扫描我要把这些
defaults just as they are and I'm going
默认原样，我要走了
to click update and it's gonna show you
点击更新，它就会显示给你
a preview of what's going to be traced
预览将要跟踪的内容
in the preview window here now for these
现在在这里的预览窗口中为这些
default settings this worked pretty well
默认设置这一功能运行良好
that's exactly what I'm looking to do
这正是我想要做的
right there if yours didn't come out as
就在那里，如果你的结果不是
well you may have to adjust these
好的，您可能需要调整一下这些。
settings a little bit and play with them
一点设置，然后再玩一玩
a little bit may even want to change the
有些人甚至可能想要更改
the type of a trace that you do here but
您在这里所做的跟踪类型，但是
this worked well for me so I was going
这对我来说很好，所以我要去
to click OK and it's going to generate a
单击OK，它将生成一个
vector copy right on top of that so let
向量复制就在上面，所以让
me close out of that menu I'm gonna take
我把我要拿的那份菜单关掉了
this if I move this out of the way you
如果我把这个移开，这会妨碍你
can see now this is the vector copy this
现在可以看到这是矢量副本这是
is the original this is the vector and
是原始的，这是向量，
I'll zoom in on that just to show you
我会放大它，只是为了给你展示一下
that is indeed a vector copy you can
这确实是一种矢量复制，你可以
grab the nodes tool and you can edit
抓起结点工具，即可编辑
those nodes individually like you would
像您一样单独处理这些节点
with any other vector object so what you
任何其他向量对象，所以您可以
can do is now you can color that in you
现在你能做的就是给你的身体涂上颜色
can do whatever you want with that one
你可以用那个做任何你想做的
thing you may notice is that the filled
您可能会注意到，填充的
in area right here the filled in area
在这里的区域中，填充区域
where is white is now negative space its
哪里是白色，哪里现在是负空间
transparency in there if you're okay
如果你还好的话，里面的透明度
with that then you're good to go if
有了这个，你就可以走了，如果
you'd like to fill that in with the
你想在上面填上
color or fill it in
给它上色或填入
white as I did here you can use the
像我在这里做的那样白，你可以用
bucket fill tool for that so let me make
水桶填充工具，让我来做
this black the way it was before
这是黑色的，就像以前一样
let me grab the bucket fill tool and I'm
让我拿起水桶灌装工具，我
gonna click on that that empty space
我要点击那个空白处
right there to fill it in now it filled
就在那里填满它，现在它填满了
it in with the color black I'm just
它和黑色很配，我只是
gonna change this to red to annouce so I
我要把这个改成红色，这样我就
can see the difference here and if you
我可以在这里看到区别，如果你
notice it's sticking out of the edges a
请注意，它是从边缘伸出的
little bit so I'm going to change that
所以我要改变这一点
by going to path dynamic offset and I'm
通过转到路径动态偏移，我
going to take this little note up here
我要把这张小纸条拿上来
and just pull that out so that it
把它拿出来，这样它就能
believes out into the design like that
就像这样相信设计
now let me finalize that by going to
现在让我通过以下几点来结束这一点：
path object to path let me go back to
PATH对象到PATH让我回到
the Select tool and I want to lower this
选择工具和我想要降低这个
to the bottom I'm gonna click this
到底部，我要点击这个
button that says lower selection to the
按钮，该按钮表示较低的选择范围
bottom and now it's lowered beneath the
底部，现在它降到了下面
design there and I can make that white
在那里设计，我可以把它变成白色
and as you can see that is no longer
如你所见，这已经不再是
transparent that is now filled with
透明的，现在填充了
white and down here you could do the
白色的，在这里你可以做
same thing because this is negative
同样的事情，因为这是负数
space as well so that's the auto trace
空间也是如此，所以这是自动跟踪
that's the automated way of tracing a
这是一种自动跟踪
vector copy of your logo if that doesn't
向量复制您的徽标，如果不是这样
work because that feature won't always
工作，因为该功能并不总是
work for more elaborate designs if your
更精细的设计，如果您的
design is it maybe it's like not a high
设计是，也许它不像是一种高
enough resolution that that feature can
足够分辨率，使该功能可以
work you'll have to manually trace a
工作时，您必须手动跟踪
copy of that using the Bezier a pen so
用贝塞尔钢笔复制
let me show you how to do that now the
现在让我向您演示如何做到这一点
first thing I want to do over here is
我想要做的第一件事是
open up the filling stroke menu with
使用打开填充笔划菜单
this button over here the keyboard
这里的这个按钮是键盘
shortcut would be ctrl shift F on to
快捷键是ctrl Shift F on to
take the original logo right here and I
把原来的徽标拿在这里，然后我
want to bring me opacity down in half so
想把我的不透明度降低一半吗？
I can see what I'm doing as a trace over
我可以看到我在做什么，作为一个痕迹
it and I want to grab the Bezier pen
它和我想要拿到贝塞尔笔
which is over here or you could press B
在这里，或者你可以按B键
on the keyboard and depending on the
在键盘上，并根据
type of design you have this design has
您的设计类型这个设计有
a lot of curves and bends and contours
很多曲线、弯道和轮廓线
and stuff for this sort of design I want
以及我想要的这种设计的东西
to use the b-spline setting of the tool
使用工具的B样条线设置的步骤
I'm gonna click b-splines
我要点击B-Splines
what this does is it basically forces
它所做的基本上是迫使
you to draw curved lines it's kind of
你画曲线，这有点像
like training wheels for the pen tool if
就像钢笔工具的辅助轮，如果
you've never used the pen tool before
您以前从未使用过钢笔工具
this is a great option to use because it
这是一个很好的选择，因为它
forces you to draw curved lines that
迫使您绘制曲线，
will be able that'll make it easier for
将能够使它更容易
you to trace this design right here so
你在这里追踪这个设计，所以
let me get rid of that I'm gonna go
让我把它处理掉，我要走了
ahead and start tracing around this
往前走，开始追踪这个
design right here and to move the page
在这里进行设计并移动页面
around basic functions I'm just pressing
围绕基本功能，我只是按下
down the mouse wheel I'm moving the
我正在向下移动鼠标滚轮
mouse and to zoom in and out I'm holding
鼠标和我手中的放大和缩小
ctrl and rolling up and down the mouse
Ctrl键并上下滚动鼠标
wheel so I'm just going to go around and
方向盘所以我要绕一圈
points going around the design over here
围绕着这里的设计点子
to trace to trace a shape going around
追踪以追踪周围的形状
the logo and if at any point you need to
徽标，如果您在任何时候需要
create a sharp corner because this tool
创建锐角，因为此工具
setting will not allow you to create
设置将不允许您创建
corners by default what you can do is
默认情况下，您可以做的是
just hold shift and then click and then
只需按住Shift键，然后单击，然后
it'll allow you to create a corner as
它将允许您创建一个角作为
you can see there but I'll be
你可以看到那里，但我会在那里
demonstrating that in a minute when I go
当我走的时候，马上证明这一点
over this area right here so let me undo
就在这片区域上，让我解开
that I'm gonna go and trace over this
我要去追查这件事
logo really quickly I'm just gonna do a
很快地，我要做一个
very quick and rudimentary tracing of
非常快速和基本的跟踪
this because I'm not actually trying to
这是因为我不是真的想
make a copy of this logo I'm just doing
复制我正在做的这个徽标
this for a demonstration
这是一个演示
okay so once you're finished tracing
好的，那么一旦你完成了追踪
around your object here you can just
在您的对象周围，您只需
click on the original node right there
单击此处的原始节点
to close the path and if you zoom out
关闭路径并缩小的步骤
you can see let me grab the Select tool
您可以看到，让我抓起选择工具
move this you can see we've traced a
移动这个，你可以看到我们已经追踪到一个
shape over that shape right there so let
就在那个形状上，所以让我们
me put that back what I want to do now
我把它放回我现在想做的事
is trace this other shape right here so
就在这里追踪另一个形状，所以
let me go back to the Bessie a penny let
让我回贝茜吧一分钱让
me zoom in I'm going to start tracing
我放大，我要开始追踪
around to this and this is where I'd
关于这个，这就是我想要的
like to demonstrate the the corner
想要示范一下角落里的
feature so I'm gonna bring this over
所以我要把这个拿过来
here like this and again right here we
在这里，就像这样，又在这里，我们
have a sharp corner so I'm gonna hold
有一个急转弯，所以我会坚持
shift and click and there you go now you
按住Shift键并单击，现在就可以了
have a sharp corner same thing up here
在这上面有一个尖角一样的东西
we have another corner area hold shift
我们还有另一个拐角区域按兵不动
click in fact for the rest of these
事实上，点击查看其余内容
points I'm gonna be holding shift the
我将持有的分数将轮班
whole time to create sharp corners like
一直在创造尖锐的角落，就像
that until we get right there and now I
直到我们到了那里，现在我
collect all of shift and get back to
收集所有的班次并返回到
tracing around this design like this now
现在就像这样画这个设计
like I said before this b-spline setting
就像我之前说的，这个b-样条线设置
in this tool it's pretty much like
在这个工具中，它很像
training wheels for the pen tool there's
钢笔工具的辅助轮有
easier there's easier ways to do this if
在以下情况下，有更容易的方法来完成此操作
you're more advanced with using this
你用这个更高级了
software but this tutorial is not for
软件，但本教程不适用于
advanced users this tutorial is for
本教程面向的高级用户
newcomers to Inkscape who just need to
Inkscape的新来者只需要
create a vector tracing of a logo that
创建徽标的矢量跟踪
they have in PNG format so let me go
他们有PNG格式的，所以让我走吧
ahead and finish tracing this back to
继续，并完成对此的追查
the starting point like that looking
起点就是这样的样子
pretty good now I'm gonna go ahead and
很好，现在我要继续了
trace this part down here as well
把这部分也追踪到这里
okay so as you can see I have finished
好的，如你所见，我已经完成了
up I've went and created these shapes as
在上面，我将这些形状创建为
well and the shape and that shape as
嗯，这个形状和那个形状就像
well so I don't know what to do now is
所以我不知道现在该做什么
we have the shape we have the designs
我们有形状，我们有设计
wrong we just have to color it in now so
错了，我们现在只需要给它上色，所以
let me grab the Select tool let me click
让我抓起选择工具让我点击
on the original logo at the back there
在后面的原始标志上
at the bottom and bring the opacity of
在底部，并带来不透明的
that all the way back up now I'm just
一路回升，现在我只是
gonna move this out of the way for now
现在我要把这件事移开
if you want to color your design in with
如果你想在你的设计中加入
the same color as your original design
和你原来设计的颜色一样
head what you can do is you could just
头你能做的就是你可以
click on the shape grab the dropper tool
单击形状抓取滴管工具
which is over here and then grab a
就在这里，然后抓起一个
selection of that color now this is just
那个颜色的选择现在这只是
black and white so I mean I could just
黑白的，所以我的意思是我可以
click the black and white colors down
点击下面的黑白颜色
here but I'm doing this assuming that
但我这么做的前提是
your logo that you're trying to check
您要检查的徽标
trace is in color so I'm going to show
痕迹是彩色的，所以我要展示
you how to do this as if this were in
你如何做到这一点就像这是在
color let me go back to the select tool
颜色让我回到选择工具
click on this shape I want to make that
点击这个形状，我想做那个
white as well
怀特也是如此
if you notice you can't see the white
如果你注意到你看不到白色
there because it's a white background
因为它是白色的背景
it's it's blending in against it but it
它是它在与它对抗，但它
is indeed filled with white let me go
确实充满了白色，让我走吧
back to the dropper fill that in with
回到滴管，填上
white and I want to get rid of that
怀特和我想摆脱它
those black outlines as well to get rid
那些黑色的轮廓也可以去掉
of the black outline just hold shift and
只需按住Shift键并
click on the red X down here now let me
点击下面的红色X，现在让我
go back to the Select tool let me take
返回到选择工具，让我选择
this shape I wanna get rid of that black
这个形状，我想摆脱那个黑色
outline as well I'm gonna hold shift
轮廓也一样，我要按住Shift
click on the X and then finally I'm
点击X，然后我终于
gonna make the larger shape over here
我要在这里做一个更大的形状
I'm gonna make that black hold shift
我要做那个黑色的轮班
click on the X click this shape do the
点击X，点击这个形状做
same thing just fill it in with its
同样的事情只需要用它的
intended colors you can use the dropper
目标颜色您可以使用滴管
tool like I did previously or you can
工具，就像我之前做的那样，或者您可以
just fill it in manually with these
只需手动填写这些内容即可
colors down here like I'm doing there's
颜色就像我在这里做的那样
also other ways you can fill you can
还有其他你可以填满的方式，你可以
choose based on RGB HSL if you have like
如果您喜欢，请选择基于RGB HSL
an HTML like a hex code for your for
类似于For的十六进制代码的HTML
your design you'd like to fill it with
你想用来填充它的设计
you can put it right there
你可以把它放在那里
followed by FF so what I'm going to do
然后是FF，所以我接下来要做的是
now is I'm going to convert this to a
现在我要把这个转换成一个
path I'm going to select over everything
我要在一切之上选择一条路
click and drag over everything and go to
单击并拖动所有内容，然后转到
path object to path and that's gonna
路径对象到路径，这将是
change that from be spline shapes to
将其从样条线形状更改为
actual true vector paths now we can take
现在我们可以选择真正的矢量路径
the original logo and get rid of that
原来的徽标，然后去掉它
and as you can see we've finished we
如你所见，我们已经完成了
have traced our vector logo so all we
追踪了我们的矢量标志，所以我们所有人
have to do now is save a vector file
现在要做的就是保存一个矢量文件
effective copy of it so to do that I'll
它的有效副本，所以为了做到这一点，我将
go to file save as and I'm going to save
转到文件另存为，我将保存
it as a dot SVG file or in Inkscape SVG
它作为点SVG文件或在Inkscape SVG中
file or if you'd like to export it as a
文件，或者如果您想将其导出为
PNG like let's say you
PNG就像我们说的你
want to enlarge it let's say the whole
想把它放大，比方说整个
point of vectorizing your logo is that
将您的徽标矢量化的要点是
you could enlarge it like that and then
你可以把它放大，然后
export a copy of it what you can do is
导出它的副本您可以做的是
go to file export PNG image and then
转到文件导出PNG图像，然后
from here you can choose export as you
从这里您可以选择导出作为您的
can click on that choose your name and
可以点击选择您的名字和
location right there and then click
位置就在那里，然后点击
export to export it and I think that
出口到出口，我认为
should do it for this tutorial so that
应该在本教程中这样做，以便
is how you can go about creating a
是如何创建一个
vector copy of your rasterized PNG logos
您的网格化PNG徽标的载体副本
with Inkscape if you have any questions
如果您有任何疑问，请使用Inkscape
leave a comment below and as always
在下面一如既往地留下评论
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]